<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Travel Places</string>
    <string name="goa">The best time to visit Goa will be from the months of November to February. You can reach Goa by Air and the major airport there is Dabolim International Airport. There is also a cheaper option to reach Goa which is by train. The major railway stations to reach Goa are the Madgaon Railway Station and Thivim Railway Station. Another interesting way to reach Goa is through a ferry from Mumbai.

</string>
    <string name="assam">Assam is a beautiful land overwhelmed by the landscapes, flora and fauna. The wildlife expedition is different from any other safari that you had taken. You can fancy yourself a jungle walk and boat ride if you visit the place during the months of November to April. As you navigate along the Brahmaputra river, you can witness the animals in their most natural habitats. Assam is one of the most naturally beautiful habitats and is one of the best places to visit in India.</string>
    <string name="leh_ladakh">Leh-Ladakh is one of the best places to visit in India’s hands down. It is the go-to destination for all travellers looking for an adventurous vacation. A trip to this place is filled with various amazing elements such as the winding bike rides, tent stay in the middle of nowhere and much more. All of this at a chilling temperature of around 15-25 degrees celsius.

</string>
    <string name="cherraounji">Cherrapunji is the place to visit in India for a distinctive experience and have the best of times while embracing nature. It is one of the surreal experiences you’ll have and provides you with a relieving break from routine. The best way to reach Cherrapunji is by Railway and the Guwahati railway station is the nearest one. You can also reach there by Air but the nearest airport Lokpriya Gopinath Bordoloi International Airport in Guwahati is 163 km away from Cherrapunji.</string>
    <string name="andaman">If you are or hydrophile or a hydrophobe, Andaman is the perfect place for you to embrace your water love or to break past your fear of water. You can get into the deep seas and take part in the amazing marine life. You will end up craving for more of this experience. This aquatic paradise in one of the best places to visit in India if you are especially if you have an Atlantean soul.</string>

</resources>